beginnersbook.com 2019-09-25

# Privacy Policy - EasySteps2BuildWebsite

If you have any questions or require any more information about beginnersbook privacy policy, please feel free to email us at chaitanyasingh.infy@gmail.com

At Beginnersbook, we take privacy of our visitors very seriously. This “Privacy Policy” page will help you understand, what personal information is collected by Beginnersbook and how it is used. We take extreme measures to protect your personal information so that it doesn’t get misused. Your name and email address that you may leave while dropping a comment on beginnersbook.com will never be shared with any third parties.

## What information Does BeginnersBook Gather about You?

**Personal Information while dropping comments:**  
When a visitor leaves a comment on any page/post of this website, the following data that is shown in the comment form is stored in the database:

1\. Your Name  
2\. Your email address  
3\. Your IP address and browser user agent

The IP address and browser user agent information is used for spam detection so that the comment area is not spammed by some bot or spammer. Your name and email address that you may leave while dropping a comment on beginnersbook.com will never be shared with any third parties

**Cookies:**  
When a user visits beginnersbook.com, a small piece of information known as cookie can be stored on your computer. Cookies can help identify your browser and that can store information about your preferences, which pages you have accessed or visited or any other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL [http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads) Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, BeginnersBook has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

## Links to other Websites

Occasionally you may find links to the third party websites on our pages or articles, these links are included for your references and we do not own them. We are not aware and responsible for the privacy policies on these websites.

## Privacy Policy Changes

BeginnersBook reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy page at any time.  
This page last updated on Nov 09, 2018.
